and I'm like about to cry and he's just
like hold on I'm getting married next
weekend in Pennsylvania and he'll be
there why don't you crash my wedding and
Mark
Parker
[Music]
Hello everybody welcome to this not
happening I'm your host Ari shafir and
today all the stories are about
nostalgia
you guys will absolutely love her please
get up for Miss Annie Letterman
[Music]
everybody my story is about uh my happy
place you know we all have that happy
place that we can go back to whenever
we're in dark times that place from our
childhood that just brings us back you
know makes us feel happy uh my happy
place was Camp Swatara my Quaker camp
that I went to in upstate Pennsylvania
and I remember like like when my dad and
my mom would put me in the car and they
drive me up I remember the butterflies
I'd get when I started to get we'd
approach you know the the entrance they
would drop me off and it was just like
so amazing there was just like bonfires
and friendship bracelets and
dreams like I remember the pizza Bagels
like every single thing about it and
then there was Mark Parker
um he was just like the cutest counselor
ever he was so hot he had an eyebrow
ring he knew like every lyric to every
Dave Matthews Band song that you know he
played on acoustic guitar at every
bonfire and he could up a hacky
sack like he was
just he was so hot like I was like I
didn't even know what why my underwear
was wet I just knew that like I knew two
things about that underwear that my mom
had written my name in it and that it
was soaking wet I was like baby horny I
was like what are you I love you these
feelings and all the counselors were so
cool and I loved that
camp um Camp did not love me back as
much I was just completely invisible not
cool at all like when you got older when
you were like 13 14 they would start the
counselors would start to wake up the
cool girls at night and like bring them
out to smoke weed and
drink and so I would they would like
wake me up and be like hello yes and
they're like do you mind moving over
Sarah's getting
down
and when you graduate from the camp at
14 you can apply to be a counselor and
all I wanted in my life was to be a
counselor I mean they were like living
the dream they were just like so awesome
and I was like I you know I would love
to be a camp counselor at Camp Swatara
but I'm not going to get the job so I
never applied because I was like I you
know I can't handle that rejection it'll
be too deep you know so um instead I
graduated from Camp Swatara and um um
since I couldn't you know smoke weed and
drink with the counselors I decided to
just like go back to Philadelphia and
just smoke and drink with real
criminals and I just became like a
horrible juvenile delinquent was just
stealing cars like my life just like
went completely downhill from there so I
went some really dark times uh and
really struggled with alcoholism and
drugs and really got up and I
remember a moment just staring into a
mirror just like what have you done with
your life you used to be a
camper and I wrote in a lipstick I wrote
on the mirror I wrote remember Camp
Swatara and I left it there for like
years like just years and years I never
cleaned that mirror and I would just
look at it in my dark times and it would
bring me back and I could really like
close my eyes and remember like the
morning Bell and I could remember like
the pig that they had at the little farm
I just remember the tire swings and the
zipline and like the lake and everything
and Mark Parker I mean it was just so so
incredible so then a couple years later
I quit drinking I moved to New York to
start doing stand-up comedy and I am
feeling good about myself and right then
on Facebook I get an invite to a camp
Swatara reunion and I'm like oh my God
here's my time to
shine here's my time to show them how
cool I was I wasn't invisible I'm Annie
Letterman an open Miker living in
Bushwick but I'm was just like so
excited to go and I look at it and I'm
working that weekend and I can't go to
the reunion I'm like devastated
and I go out before I go out though I go
I I take the opportunity when I realize
that I can't go to the reunion to just
friend request every counselor I ever
had just everyone across the board don't
give a if they accept me I'm
throwing it out there anyway and I go um
I go onto the subway all bummed out and
I hear from behind me I hear someone go
Annie
Letterman and I turn around and it's
this guy Dan McFarland who was one of my
Camp counselors and I'm like holy
and he's like oh my God and like first
of all I'm shocked he remembers like I
can't even believe that he remembers him
like maybe I wasn't invisible and he
goes Annie this is so crazy that I'm
running into you right now because I was
just talking to one of the other
counselors um he was talking about your
Facebook he had looked at your Facebook
and he's like was talking about how hot
you are and I was like me huh I was like
but who who was the counselor and he was
like Mark Parker and I was like oh my
God holy I was like I wanted to
him my whole life I knew what
was I wanted to this guy
I've measured every guy against him I'm
in love with him I have loved him every
day since
Camp give him to me where is he put him
inside me
now and he's like oh he doesn't live in
New York anymore and I'm like about to
cry and he's just like hold on I'm
getting married next weekend in
Pennsylvania and he'll be there why
don't you crash my wedding and Mark
Parker and I'm
like yes I'm like is Jesus real like I'm
like what is going
on I'm like I mean fate fate fate fate
I'm like this is just like going to be
the best experience so I tell everyone
like I'm going to Boda guys I'm going on
the subway I'm stopping homeless man I'm
like here's a quarter I'm going to
Mark Parker everyone knows I'm like this
is going to be the best day my
life Not only was it amazing that this
had happened but it's also like I was
wrong about who I was like if I had
applied to be a counselor like I might
have gotten it like I may have missed my
opportunity to live this
incredible life because how would he
know like he wouldn't losers don't get
stopped on the Subway invisible
people don't have Mark Parker saying
they're hot like so I go on his Facebook
page and I write like you're a Kil and
then in parenthesis in case he doesn't
get it I'm like a counselor I'd like to
and then I'm like that's not enough
so then I go on his on into his messages
and I'm like hey Mark let's
and he writes back like cool um yes
absolutely I'm down um so I pack my
bag it's just as suitc case filled with
underwear obviously no condoms cuz I can
party and then I like you know I pull my
little suitcase and I go in and I'm just
like I mean I can't even like describe
to how I felt I'm like I can't wait to
meet this handsome ass
man like I just I just remember him
being like so tall and dark and handsome
and like amazing and talented the way he
played crash into me I
mean and I'm like and just to see all
the counselors in general like to see my
heroes again and I like you know I like
bust through the door and it's after the
wedding because when you crash a wedding
you don't go for the ceremony you go to
obviously so I go in and I look
around and I'm like where who are these
old
people oh these are my
counselors I'm like oh holy they're
all like balding and fat and like
pregnant and I'm like it was like if
froze but they got old as
so I'm like that's cool whatever uh
Mark's going to be hot and like I'm
looking for him right and before I can
find him this woman I've never met comes
up and she goes oh my God are you Annie
and I'm like uhhuh and she's like oh my
God are you Mark's Annie and I'm like
well that's I guess and she's like he's
so excited you're coming he's been
talking about you this whole time and
I'm like that's when I realized I'm the
second most eventful thing that's
happening at this wedding besides the
nupal
like everyone's like this girl's going
to come to mark this is amazing
Mark's getting
so then um you know the dorky
parts and
um there he
is and let me tell you he still has the
eyebrow
ring he had like those long fingernails
like he still plays guitar which by the
way guys just trim them Jesus
Christ I don't need to know whether I
have HPV from your
fingernails and I'm just like holy
everything that made him cool in
the 90s makes him so unmother
now keep in mind I've quit drinking at
this point I'm sober as like there
is no way to drink him hot like this is
my lot in life at this this point
there's no other reason I'm at this
wedding than to Mark Parker like
I'm there to get
it and he comes over and he's like hey
girl I'm like
no oh he's also got gay boys Jesus
Christ I got nothing to work with
here so I'm like all right I hatch a
plan I'm like I'm I am going to get him
so
wasted that he passes out and it's his
fault he doesn't me right I'm like
sucks I was looking forward to it um so
it's the plan's working right he's
starting to bobblehead he's got cookie
monster eyes you know he's about
out and I see him he pops a pill and I'm
like
Ambien
no Aderall
so now he's
just he's just there for me guys and I'm
like and he was like so nice you know so
I had to him I had to what was I
going to be like this whole reason I
came I couldn't be all a sudden like I'm
not ready not ready I aggressively was
like I'm going you I'm going to
your dick I don't know if you know
what body part I'm going to it's
your
dick like at least we'll go back to his
like nice room with this nice bed and
breakfast no he didn't have have his own
room I Mark Parker on the pullout
couch in another counselor's
room so the sex was great just kidding
uh
terrible at one point uh he goes down on
me and he looks up and he goes M
delicious like he's making a Yelp review
of my
[Music]
like o delicious can we both be
shot can we be taken out by snipers
right now like someone should die after
someone says that so humiliating
and I'm just like in my own personal
Vietnam I'm like oh my God how do I get
out of this so I close my eyes and I try
to go to my happy place but all that's
in my happy place is M delicious I'm
like God damn it I my happy
place oh my God but I like after the
deed is done and everything's been wet
napped up uh
um I just like go to bed
feeling you know grossed out like I
ruined camp for myself but at least I
saved camp for him and he now goes to
bed knowing that he's preserved this you
know this Crush in this relationship
that he's always imagined having to so I
go to bed a hero and then I wake up from
those sweet sweet dreams um to Mark
watching me sleep which is always
delightful what way to wake up ah my
life is in danger terrifying just to
have your mistakes just right in your
face like ah the glistening from the
eyebrow ring
great so he um you know he's staring at
me and I go oh hello um and he goes you
know what I was looking at you watching
you sleep and I'm realizing I think I do
remember you from camp
now
I'm like about to cry he didn't remember
me from Camp yes I was invisible yes I
was a loser do you know who I was to him
some stranger that friend
requested him on Facebook and then was
like I'm going to your dick and
then I him I was just the chick
from
Facebook so I guess moral of the story
is don't rape yourself with someone
else's
body and never go back to your happy
place don't your happy
place uh my only issue with telling the
story is that Mark is like so nice you
know he's like such a good person and
I'm just so afraid he's going to see
this you know and I'm going to feel so
guilty and have to him again you
guys thank you you so
[Music]
much